If you're not
We apologize
And won't bother you again
If you are
I can cooperate with the verification
But keep it a secret until the results are out
And of course don't let it affect my wife
Rest assured Ms Su
The Fu Group won't put unnecessary pressure on you
Mrs Fu
It's Mrs Fu
Can I ask one last question
Go ahead
When you were little did you
Remember a ginkgo tree
Hyah
Uncomfortable
Seems a bit familiar
Mr Fu thank you for being willing to verify this
Mr Fu will later cooperate with the Fu Group
To verify some private matters
Today's project meeting will continue
Ah
In the past life Fu Chenzhou passively returned to the Fu family
In this life
He chose to face his identity on his own
Not pushed by others
Neither panicking nor running away